Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors but lower
in calories and higher in protein. This
is Minter Wonderland.
>> Wow. Texture is fantastic. Coming back
in.
>> Yeah.
>> You don't even like chocolate mint. I
don't like chocolate mint, but the
chocolate base is so good. It's worth
it. So rich. Really good. I think it's
one of the best ones I've ever made.
>> It's really good.
>> Given all that, let me show you how to
make it. We're doing a dark chocolate
peppermint base. So, a chocolate protein
shake, an 1/8 of a teaspoon of pepper
extract, and all these dry ingredients
you see on screen. We're going to blend
that all up with an immersion blender,
and then throw it in the freezer for at
least 16 hours. Once it's completely
frozen through, you can take it out, run
under hot water for 30 to 60 seconds,
and then throw it in your Ninja Creamy
on the light ice cream setting. Once
that's done spinning, it might be a
little bit powdery. That's completely
normal. You're just going to scrape down
the sides with a butter knife. Add three
Oreo thins. I removed the cream to save
a few calories. Obviously, that's
completely optional. And then five grams
of these Lucky Charms style
marshmallows. You can find these at a
ton of grocery stores now and recently
they've been one of my favorite Ninja
Creamy mixins. Then we'll just run it on
the mixing setting. Top it with the rest
of our marshmallows and then you're good
to go. Let me know down in the comments
which Ben & Jerry's flavor I should
recreate next.